govliquidation.com 2019-06-11

# Privacy Policy - Liquidity Services

## Who is Liquidity Services?

Liquidity Services, Inc., owner and operator of the websites [www.liquidityservices.com](https://www.liquidityservices.com/), [www.networkintl.com](http://www.networkintl.com/), [www.go-dove.com](http://www.go-dove.com/), [www.govliquidation.com](http://www.govliquidation.com/), [www.liquidation.com](http://www.liquidation.com/), [www.direct.liquidation.com](http://direct.liquidation.com/), [www.govdeals.com](http://www.govdeals.com/), [www.auctiondeals.com](http://www.auctiondeals.com/), [http://international.go-dove.com](http://international.go-dove.com/), [www.irondirect.com](http://www.irondirect.com/), [www.assetzone.com](https://www.assetzone.com/Login.aspx?h=1), and [www.secondipity.com](http://www.secondipity.com/) (each a “Website” and collectively the “Websites”) through its various subsidiaries (collectively, “Liquidity Services”, “us” “we” or “our”), wants you to know that we take your privacy seriously. Because we do, our Website Privacy Policy states what information we collect and how that information is collected, for what purposes we collect information, how that information is used, who we share it with and under what circumstances that information would be released. We want you to know when you have a choice regarding the collection or dissemination of any personal information, and how you can exercise your options. Our Website Privacy Policy will also explain what rights you have in relation to your personal information, what steps we take to secure your private information and what steps you should take to safeguard that information. Finally, our Website Privacy Policy will tell you who you can contact regarding questions about our Website Privacy Policy.

## What Information Do We Collect?

We collect only the information that is necessary to provide the services offered via our Website, to comply with our legal obligations, to facilitate transactions with you, and to gather information about general Website traffic on our various Websites, and no additional information other than is necessary will be requested of you without first clearly informing you of the collection and use of such additional information. Among the information we collect there will be personal information. This means information that identifies you personally such as your name or contact details or data that can be linked with such information in order to identify you.

### Information We Collect When You Register for an Account on Our Website

When you register for an account with us through any of our Websites, we may collect information from you such as:

  * Your name
  * Your telephone number
  * Your email address
  * Your address (including, city, state, postal code, and country)
  * Business name (if applicable)
  * Number of employees (if applicable)
  * VAT / tax number
  * Customer information, including the password chosen by you to access your account

We may request additional information from you depending on certain transaction, contractual or regulatory requirements. We will notify you of what information we need, and how it will be used. This information is used to contact you to answer your questions about us and to complete auctions, confirm purchases and conclude other transactions you have initiated with or through us.

### Information We Collect from Persons Who Access Websites

We also collect information about you and your computer when you click on any of our Websites. We log your IP address, browser type, access times, and referring site to help diagnose potential problems with our server, to administer our Websites, track and report website traffic and potentially for marketing purposes. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information.

Our Websites use cookies to keep track of your user account. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your username so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit one of our Websites, and for other purposes. For our site to function properly, it is important you have cookies enabled.

See the cookies section below for more information on cookies.

## How Do We Collect Personal Information About You?

Most of the personal information we collect about you is information voluntarily provided by you when you contact us or submit information to us, such as a registration, bid submission, purchase, resume, investor inquiry, end-use-certificate, or other communications. Other personal information is available to us when you click on any Website and is collected electronically via our web engine. Other personal information may be obtained by us from publicly available sources from time to time.

## Why Do We Collect Personal Information about You?

We collect personal information to establish a business relationship with you, consummate transactions with you, facilitate doing business with you, and/or to respond to an enquiry by you.

Where we require personal information on you to perform any of the above and you do not decline to provide such personal information (as is your right), we may not be able to provide the relevant services to you.

## How Do We use your Personal Information?

Personal information collected by us is used to communicate with you and generally to facilitate doing business with you. We use the information provided by you to communicate with you regarding your specific inquiries.

We do not sell or release your personal information to any third party (except as set out in this Privacy Policy) without your consent, unless we are required to by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with an official investigation by a law enforcement organization.

We will also send you information regarding upcoming auctions, sales events and our services. If you choose, we will include information about specific asset sales you designate when you register for an account with us.

We may use your personal information to enhance or develop features, products and services.

## What is the Basis for Processing?

Data protection laws require that there is a specific lawful basis for processing. Where you provide personal information to us for the purposes of an enquiry, the basis for processing is that it is required as a legitimate interests of ours as a business to respond to your enquiry.

Where we process your personal information for the purposes of sending you marketing communications (such as buy alert emails, information on upcoming sales events, special announcements, etc), we will rely upon the legal basis of legitimate interests and/or consent (if obtained) for processing your personal information for those purposes.

Where we enter into a business relationship with you, we rely on the legal basis of performance of a contract with you for processing your personal information on the basis of that contractual relationship and to complete a transaction with you. Where we use your personal information to enhance or develop features, products and services we rely on the legal basis of legitimate interest as it is necessary for our legitimate interest to provide a responsive service to our customers to keep them satisfied.

Before we alter the reason for using any personal information you have provided to us, we will notify you of our intended change in use of that information, ensuring such use complies with applicable data protection law and where necessary obtain your consent prior to using your personal information in a new way.

## Who Do We Share your Personal Information with?

We may provide other Website users, our vendors, our service providers and partners with information on a winning bid or to confirm a purchase and sale, or as required in order to provide services to you.

We may share your personal information internally within our group of business entities.

We may provide transaction-related information to government or private auditors to inspect or validate our business practices, accounting records, or financial reports. Any release of information for such a purpose will be done under standard confidentiality restrictions.

We may share your personal information with third party vendors such as Salesforce, Oracle Eloqua, Amazon Web Services and Microsoft Azure whose services we may utilise from time to time to assist us in our provision of services to you. We may share anonymized traffic data with third parties.

As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or merges with us your personal information will be disclosed to such entity. Also, where we carry out an asset sale of a particular business division, your personal information (if held by such business division) may be considered an asset of ours and as such it is possible it will be sold or transferred to the purchasing third party.

We may share your information with third party partners or service providers with whom we will jointly provide or alternatively outsource the provision of the services requested by you to, or financing institution partners who may offer financial products to you. These third party financial institution partners will use your personal information to send you marketing communications only if you have requested their services. We will only share your information where it is lawful and required for the provision of services to you or where you have consented to this.

## Do we Transfer Your Personal Information Outside Your Country?

Your personal information shall generally be stored and processed in the US. Your personal data may be stored and processed in any country where we or our affiliates or approved partners have facilities or operations, including but not limited to the UK, Hong Kong and China.

From time to time there may be transfers between members of our group of business entities into and/or out of the European Economic Area (EEA).

For all cross-border transfers of personal information we ensure appropriate security measures and legal safeguards are in place.

For EU Residents:

Where your personal information is transferred from within the EEA to a country outside the EEA (including the United States) we ensure that security measures and adequate safeguards are in place for the transfer of personal information in compliance with applicable data protection laws on the transfer of personal information outside the EEA.

To find out more about how we safeguard your personal information (including obtaining a copy of such safeguards) in relation to transfers outside the EEA, please contact us via the details provided in the contact us section below.

## How Long Do We Retain Your Personal Information?

We retain your personal information for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the information is collected and in line with this Privacy Policy. When determining the relevant retention periods, we will take into account factors including:

  * contractual obligations to you;
  * legal obligation(s) under applicable law to retain data for a certain period of time;
  * statute of limitations under applicable law;
  * (potential) disputes; and
  * guidelines issued by relevant national data protection regulators.

Otherwise, we securely anonymise or erase your personal information once it is no longer required. For further information about how long we will keep your personal information, please contact us using the contact details provided in the contact us section below.

## What are My Rights?

### Notice to California Residents

Under California Civil Code §§ 1798.80-1798.85 and California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575 – 22579, California residents are entitled to the following rights pertaining to protecting their personal information. Residents have the right to reasonable security of their personal information by us, and to destruction of any personal information that is no longer to be retained by the company via shredding, erasing or otherwise modifying the personal information in the records to make them indecipherable. Residents may expect that a business that discloses personal information about a California resident under a contract with a non-affiliated third party shall require by contract that the third party implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information, to protect the personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure. Residents have a right to timely notification by us if we learn of an unauthorized disclosure or acquisition of your personal information. Residents have the right to be informed by our customer relations staff of how they can inquire about our privacy practices or compliance with the above-referenced California laws. Residents have the right to be provided contact information for inquiring about the company’s privacy practices at every location in California where we do business. Residents have a right to a response to any enquiry regarding our privacy practices or compliance with California law within 30 days of receipt of the enquiry by us. We may not request you waive any of your rights under the above-referenced California laws.

### Notice to European Union Residents

Under EU Regulation 2016/679 of the European Parliament and the Council; the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), you have a number of rights when it comes to your personal information. Further information and advice about your rights can be obtained from the data protection regulator in your country of residence within the EU. You can exercise any of these rights by writing to us on the email address below in the contact us section below:

**The right to be informed**. You have the right to be provided with clear, transparent and easily understandable information about how we use your information and your rights. This is why we’re providing you with the information in this Policy.

**The right of access**. You have the right to obtain access to your information (if we’re processing it), and certain other information (similar to that provided in this Privacy Policy). This is so you’re aware and can check that we’re using your information in accordance with data protection law. You can do this by writing us on the email address below.

**The right to rectification**. You are entitled to have your information corrected if it is inaccurate or incomplete. You can request that we rectify any errors in personal information that we hold by writing us on the email address below.

**The right to erasure**. This is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’ and, in simple terms, enables you to request the deletion or removal of your information where there is no compelling reason for us to keep using it. This is not a general right to erasure; there are exceptions.

**The right to restrict processing**. You have rights to ‘block’ or suppress further use of your information. When processing is restricted, we can still store your information, but may not use it further.

**The right to data portability**. You have rights to obtain and reuse your personal data for your own purposes across different services. For example, if you decide to switch to a new provider, this enables you to move, copy or transfer your information easily between our IT systems and theirs safely and securely, without affecting its usability. This is not a general right however and there are exceptions.

**The right to object to processing**. You have the right to object to certain types of processing, including processing for direct marketing (i.e. receiving emails from us notifying you about other services we provide which we think may be of interest to you or being contacted with varying potential opportunities). You may change your preferences regarding email communications by contacting us or by visiting one of our preference centers listed below.

**The right to lodge a complaint**. You have the right to lodge a complaint about the way we handle or process your personal data with your national data protection regulator.

**The right to withdraw consent**. If you have given your consent to anything we do with your personal data (i.e we rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal information), you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time (although if you do so, it does not mean that anything we have done with your personal data with your consent up to that point is unlawful). You can withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal information at any time.

We usually act on requests and provide information free of charge but may charge a reasonable fee to cover our administrative costs of providing the information for baseless or excessive/repeated requests, or further copies of the same information. Alternatively, we may be entitled to refuse to act on the request.

Please consider your request responsibly before submitting it. We will respond as soon as we can. Generally, this will be within one month from when we receive your request but, if the request is going to take longer to deal with, we’ll come back to you and let you know.

## Choice / Opt-Out / Deletion

Upon registration, our site provides users the opportunity to elect to receive Buyer Alert emails. Generally, you may change your preferences regarding communications at the links below or by contacting us.

## What Steps Do We Take to Secure Your Personal Information?

Employees having access to personal information must undergo data privacy training and are monitored by management to ensure that adequate safeguards are used to protect the private information of our customers. Our Websites have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Our Websites use SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption for all sensitive data transmitted over the Internet. This includes customers adding data to the Website, and employees transmitting data off the Website. No information, including the passwords that would give access to sensitive information, ever flows over the Internet un-encrypted.

## Do We Return Your Personal Information?

A user may request we discontinue the use of that person’s personal information. If you would like to know what information we have collected, would like any information purged, or would like for us to discontinue using personal information, please contact privacy@liquidityservices.com. The return of certain personal information by us may prevent you from accessing all or certain portions of our Websites, and we will endeavour to communicate to you the extent to which your request will affect your use of our Websites prior to complying with your request.

## How Can I Protect My Personal Information?

Never send credit card information via email. Do not release information about your account to anyone who is not authorized by you to transact business with us on your behalf. Do not tell your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password to verify your identity.

## Do We Use Cookies?

Cookies are small text files stored by your device when you access most of our Websites on the internet. We will use two types of cookies:

  * Session cookies – these expire when you close your browser and leave your computer.
  * Persistent cookies – these are stored in the longer term on your computer. They are normally used to make sure the site remembers your preferences.

We use cookies to make it easier to use and to support the provision of information and functionality to you. Cookies also provide us with information about how our Websites are used so we can keep them as up to date, relevant and error free as possible. By using our Websites, you agree to our using cookies. Certain cookies may be set the moment you visit any Website.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, preventing cookies is likely to impact the functionality or performance of our Websites, or prevent you from using certain services provided through them. If you prevent cookies, we cannot guarantee access to the services provided through our Websites or be sure how our Websites will perform during your visit. Preventing cookies will also affect our ability to update our Websites to cater to your user preferences and improve its performance.

Most internet browsers are initially set up to automatically accept cookies. You can change the settings to block cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent to your device. If you use different devices to view and access the Site (e.g. your computer, smartphone, tablet etc) you will need to ensure that each browser on each device is adjusted to suit your cookie preferences.

Disable Cookies in Internet Explorer >> [Click here](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)

Disable Cookies in Chrome >> [Click here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)

Disable Cookies in Safari >> [Click here](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US)

Disable Cookies in FireFox >> [Click here](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)

Disable Cookies in Safari IOS >> [Click here](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)

Disable Cookies in Google Android >> [Click here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/114662?hl=en&ref_topic=3422740&visit_id=1-636620373197955657-2307514473&rd=1)

[Click here for more information on Cookies and how to manage them.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/)

## How Can I Contact You About My Personal Information?

If you believe that your personal information has been improperly released by us to a third party or if you have questions about how we collect, store, use, or destroy your personal information, or how to exercise your rights in relation to your personal information you may contact us at the email address, telephone number, or mailing address listed below. When contacting us about your personal information, please do not include your account password, credit card number, date of birth, driver license number, or social security number in any email to us.

You can always change personal information such as your address, email address, or phone number through the Profiles section of My Account on the Website. Credit card information can be changed when you bid in a sales event.

If you experience difficulty in correcting personal information or have questions regarding our Website Privacy Policy, please contact one of our customer service centers at the contact information on our Websites, or reach us by mail at:  
Data Protection Officer  
Liquidity Services  
6931 Arlington Road, Ste. 200  
Bethesda, MD 20814

If you wish to file a complaint about our collection, use, disclosure, or protection of your personal information or if you have specific questions about our policies or practices regarding collection, retention, use, or disclosure of personal information, please contact us at [privacy@liquidityservices.com](mailto:privacy@liquidityservices.com).

**Liquidity Services  
6931 Arlington Road, Ste. 200, Bethesda, MD 20814  
Tel. (202) 467-6868** **(202) 467-6868; Fax (202) 467-5475**

Revised May 15, 2018
